A Guide to the Papers of Collins Denny 1872-1943
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Collins Denny Correspondence
  - 1900-1910
    - James Atkins to Collins Denny 1900 August 14-1923 March 22 (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Brown Ayres to Collins Denny 1904 August 14-1910 January 17 (Box-folder 8:11)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; A's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 8:12)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; A's 1872-1910 (Box-folder 8:13)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 8:14)
      re: Baltimore Conference
    - C. F. Bates to Collins Denny 1903 February 4-1910 May 7 (Box-folder 8:15)
    - W. O. Beasley to Collins Denny 1910 November 1-1911 August 1 (Box-folder 8:16)
    - W. B. Beauchamp to Collins Denny 1910 May 17-1927 October 26 (Box-folder 8:17)
    - Bishop H. A. Boaz to Collins Denny 1909 March 4-1937 September 21 (Box-folder 8:18)
    - B. W. Bond to Collins Denny 1900 May 1-1917 January 11 (Box-folder 8:19)
    - C. H. Briggs to Collins Denny 1910 November 7-1912 April 11 (Box-folder 8:20)
    - W. L. Britton to Collins Denny 1910 November 13-1910 November 25 (Box-folder 8:21)
    - Chas. L. Brooks to Collins Denny 1910 December 2-1916 April 4 (Box-folder 8:22)
    - N. P. Bryan to Collins Denny 1901 August 17-1910 January 29 (Box-folder 8:23)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; B's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 8:24)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 8:25)
    - Rich Campbell to Collins Denny 1904 April 28-1904 September 7 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - J. E. Carpenter to Collins Denny 1910 May 27-1914 May 30 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - H. K. Carrol to Collins Denny 1902 February 4-1920 December 4 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - J. F. Caskey to Collins Denny 1910 November. 1-1911 July 11 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - F. H. Chalmers to Collins Denny 1902 June 13-1914 March 23 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Churchill Chamberlayne to Collins Denny 1906 July 25-1918 November 6 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - E. D. Chappel to Collins Denny 1910 July 2-1910 August 31 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 9:8)
      re: China Publishing House, 1902-1906
    - Charles N. Clark to Collins Denny 1912 August 12-1918 May 22 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - R. A. Clark to Collins Denny 1904 March 25-1904 April 13 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - A. E. Clement to Collins Denny 1902 November 1-1907 October 3 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - G. T. D. Collins to Collins Denny 1904 December 15-1905 December 27 (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 9:13)
      re: Condolences on death of father (William R. Denny)
    - H. S. Coe to Collins Denny 1907 January 11-1916 March 6 (Box-folder 9:14)
    - Theodore Copeland to Collins Denny 1909 January 14-1913 December 29 (Box-folder 9:15)
    - Theodore Copeland to Collins Denny 1914 January 2-1933 March 6 (Box-folder 9:16)
    - H. P. Crowe to Collins Denny 1910 June 4-1912 February 16 (Box-folder 9:17)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; C's 1872-1910 (Box-folder 9:19)
    - W. A. Dale to Collins Denny 1909 August 21-1913 February 10 (Box-folder 9:20)
    - Clara Bell Davis to Collins Denny 1902 October 25-1924 February 13 (Box-folder 9:21)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 10:1)
      re: Books of Noah K. Davis, 1907-1909
    - James E. Dickey to Collins Denny 1910 June 10-1928 March 26 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Hoyt M. Dobbs to Collins Denny 1909 February. 13-1940 September 24 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Bishop H. M. DuBose to Collins Denny 1909 July 31-1939 February 3 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Homer Eaton to Collins Denny 1902 August 25-1906 February 5 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - J. S. Engle to Collins Denny 1904 May 17-1910 March 3 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 10:9)
      re: >Episcopacy, election and congratulations
    - Collins Denny Correspondence, E's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - J. B. Fishburn to Collins Denny 1901 April 19-1910 December 22 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - J. B. Fishburn to Collins Denny 1911 January 5-1914 September 24 (Box 11:2)
    - J. B. Fishburn to Collins Denny 1915 January 4-1922 June 9 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - J. B. Fishburn to Collins Denny 1922 December 4-1942 May 27 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - W. S. Fitzgerald to Collins Denny 1905 March. 30-1909 April 4 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - U. G. Foote to Collins Denny 1910 June 30-1912 April 5 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - J. S. French to Collins Denny 1904 September 26-1928 August 15 (Box-folder 11:7)
    - H. O. Fulton to Collins Denny 1909 September 7-1922 November 29 (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; F's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Belton Gilbreath to Collins Denny 1903 October. 15-1904 January 12 (Box-folder 11:11)
    - B.B. Glasgow to Collins Denny 1901 May 20-1925 May 11 (Box-folder 11:12)
    - O. E. Goddard to Collins Denny 1910 February 25-1928 December 31 (Box-folder 11:13)
    - S. F. Goddard to Collins Denny 1910 September 5-1911 July 24 (Box-folder 11:14)
    - T. W. Goodwin to Collins Denny 1905 June 30-1911 January 19 (Box-folder 11:15)
    - John Goucher to Collins Denny 1902 June 18-1917 February 21 (Box-folder 11:16)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; G's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 11:17)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; G's 1872-1910 (Box-folder 11:18)
    - W. A. Hanna to Collins Denny 1910 June 14-1911 June 29 (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Bishop Samuel R. Hoy to Collins Denny 1909 January 3-1938 February 28 (Box-folder 12:2)
    - J. S. Hutchinson to Collins Denny 1902 February 26-1910 February 23 (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; H's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; H's 1872-1910 (Box-folder 12:5)
    - G. N. Ivey to Collins Denny 1900 February 1-1900 February 19 (Box-folder 12:6)
    - T. N. Ivey to Collins Denny 1906 [?]-1921 January 26 (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 12:8)
    - W. L. Jackson to Collins Denny 1907 June 16-1929 September 23 (Box-folder 12:9)
    - A. B. Jones to Collins Denny 1906 December 13-1924 March 8 (Box-folder 12:10)
    - L. L. Johnson to Collins Denny 1910 August 15-1912 April 8 (Box-folder 12:11)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; J's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 12:12)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 12:13)
    - W. C. Kendrick to Collins Denny 1900 September 8-1903 July 29 (Box-folder 12:14)
    - Bishop Paul Kern to Collins Denny 1910 May 12-1940 September 10 (Box-folder 12:15)
    - L. Clay Kilby to Collins Denny 1901 January 8-1910 May 23 (Box-folder 12:16)
    - Bishop John C. Kilgo to Collins Denny 1910 June 30-1921 June 30 (Box-folder 12:17)
    - P. R. Knickerbocker to Collins Denny 1909 February 12-1929 June 13 (Box-folder 12:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; K's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 12:19)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box 12:20)
    - T. V. Lambert to Collins Denny 1907 July 9-1932 October 11 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - John W. Lewis to Collins Denny 1896 February 12-1910 May 25 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - J. Reese Lin to Collins Denny 1896 June 27-1915 June 24 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - D. K. Linebaugh to Collins Denny 1910 November 4-1911 June 7 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - N. L. Linebaugh to Collins Denny 1909 September 7-1916 November 27 (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Wm. F. Locke to Collins Denny 1906 March 14-1930 March 29 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; L's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence: L's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 13:8)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 13:9)
    - R. H. Mahon to Collins Denny 1906 October 11-1922 October 24 (Box-folder 13:10)
    - I. P. Martin to Collins Denny 1908 November 28-1942 August 5 (Box-folder 13)
    - F. M. Massey to Collins Denny 1905 August 17-1915 November 6 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Arthur Mather to Collins Denny 1910 May 17-1915 November 1 (Box-folder 13:13)
    - A. F. Mathews to Collins Denny 1905 July 9-1905 July 22 (Box-folder 13:14)
    - C. L. McCauslan to Collins Denny 1909 September 9-1924 June 23 (Box-folder 13:15)
    - W. T. McClure to Collins Denny 1910 July 7-1913 September 5 (Box-folder 13:16)
    - James H. McCoy to Collins Denny 1909 February 8-1918 July 20 (Box-folder 13:17)
    - Correspondence to Bishop J. McCoy 1913 March 29-1913 May 1 (Box-folder 13:18)
    - W. F. McDowell to Collins Denny 1910 June 8-1927 March 22 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Hugh M. McIlhany to Collins Denny 1904 August 8-1907 December 2 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - C. H. McGhee to Collins Denny 1910 November 26-1911 August 4 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - W. F. Murray to Collins Denny 1907 May 24-1920 December 23 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - W. F. McMurry to Collins Denny 1921 January 3-1932 October 19 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - E. C. McVoy to Collins Denny 1910 June 7-1917 November 17 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 14:7)
    - R. W. Millsaps to Collins Denny 1901 June 2-1910 November 4 (Box-folder 14:8)
    - C. F. Mitchell to Collins Denny 1910 August 23-1912 April 30 (Box-folder 14:9)
    - J. B. Mitchell to Collins Denny 1910 May 30-1923 April 12 (Box-folder 14:10)
    - J. H. Moffat to Collins Denny 1901 April 11-1901 July 19 (Box-folder 14:11)
    - Orra P. Monnette to Collins Denny 1900 April 24-1901 October 28 (Box-folder 14:12)
    - J. W. Moore to Collins Denny 1910 November 9-1929 October 5 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Roy Moore to Collins Denny 1909 September 17-1937 November 28 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - H. O. Murfee to Collins Denny 1904 October 18-1933 December 22 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - W. B. Murray to Collins Denny 1901 June 3-1922 September 27 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; M's 1900-1910s (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence: M's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Thomas B. Nealy to Collins Denny 1910 May 20-1925 April 22 (Box-folder 15:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 15:9)
      re: Northern Methodist Church--Invasion by, 1904-1910
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; N's 15:10 (Box-folder 15:10)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 15:11)
    - A. L. Ormond to Collins Denny 1907 March 4-1925 June 26 (Box-folder 15:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; O's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 15:13)
    - Collins Denny Outgoing Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 15:14)
    - Thomas Nelson Page to Collins Denny 1905 August 8 & n.d. (Box-folder 15:15)
    - J. A. Parks to Collins Denny 1910 July 23-1910 November 24 (Box-folder 15:16)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 15:17)
      re: Peabody Chancellorship, 1900, 1901
    - John P. Pettyjohn to Collins Denny 1915 October 20-1931 October 20 (Box-folder 15:18)
    - Henry C. Pfeiffer to Collins Denny 1915 May 10-1931 October 20 (Box-folder 15:19)
    - W. W. Pinson to Collins Denny 1910 November 1-1911 November 9 (Box-folder 15:20)
    - Lewis Powell to Collins Denny 1907 December 14-1918 August 20 (Box-folder 15:21)
    - J. M Postelle to Collins Denny 1909 September 6-1910 April 30 (Box-folder 15:22)
    - Forrest Prettyman to Collins Denny 1906 April 9-1937 December 3 (Box-folder 15:23)
    - Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 15:24)
      re: Dallas Publishing House, 1899-1908
    - A. B. Pugh to Collins Denny 1906 April 13-1910 May 16 (Box-folder 15:25)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; P's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 16:3)
      re: Randolph Macon College, 1902-1909
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Collins Denny Outgoing Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Perry Rader to Collins Denny 1910 August 19-1926 July 22 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - C. O. Ransford to Collins Denny 1910 May-1937 September 3 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - E. V. Register to Collins Denny 1903 January 25-1929 September 12 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - C. S. Rennison to Collins Denny 1910 July 25-1910 August 20 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Jno. W. Rice to Collins Denny 1902 March 25-1910 May 19 (Box-folder 16:10)
    - O. M. Rickman to Collins Denny 1910 November 9-1921 November 14 (Box-folder 16:11)
    - S. M. Robinson to Collins Denny 1910 August 10-1911 May 4 (Box-folder 16:12)
    - 1905 April 6-1927 July 27 1905 April 6-1927 July 27 (Box-folder 16:13)
    - L. S. Rudasill to Collins Denny 1910 May 17-1931 November 5 (Box-folder 16:14)
    - J. B. Russell to Collins Denny 1904 January 2-1907 January 14 (Box-folder 16:15)
    - R. L. Russell to Collins Denny 1910 August 24-1931 August 7 (Box-folder 16:16)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; R's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 16:17)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; R's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 16:18)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1872-1910 (Box-folder 16:19)
    - A. L. Scales to Collins Denny 1910 June 2-1910 November 18 (Box-folder 16:20)
    - J. A. B. Scherer to Collins Denny 1902 December 8-1903 July 24 (Box-folder 16:21)
    - O. F. Sensabaugh to Collins Denny 1910 February 10-1921 February 2 (Box-folder 16:22)
    - E. A. Shugart to Collins Denny 1908 December 19-1943 April 29 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - J. W. Sims to Collins Denny 1910 June 14-1912 February 28 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - F. Osgood Smith to Collins Denny 1901 September 19-1906 September 1 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - J. W. Smith to Collins Denny 1901 August 8-1911 June 15 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - W. W. Smith to Collins Denny 1900 October 1-1901 April 30 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 17:6)
      re: The Southern Society of Philosophy and Psychology, 1904-1905
    - Lon V. Stephens to Collins Denny 1904 September 30-1913 November 1 (Box-folder 17:8)
    - Stone Printing & Manufacturing Co. to Collins Denny 1902 February 1-1910 June 30 (Box-folder 17:9)
    - J. J. Stowe to Collins Denny 1908 October 27-1910 July 22 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - J. P. Street to Collins Denny 1902 January 23-1911 August 16 (Box-folder 17:11)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; S's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 17:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; S's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 17:13)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgong Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 17:14)
    - William H. Talbat to Collins Denny 1910 May 17-1917 August 10 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - John B. Tansel to Collins Denny 1903 January 3-1905 July 11 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - S. G. Thompson to Collins Denny 1910 May 21-1911 June 15 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - W. E. Thompson to Collins Denny 1906 October 18-1915 October 1 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - T. P. Turner to Collins Denny 1910 September 23-1912 April 17 (Box-folder 18:5)
    - John Paul Tyler to Collins Denny 1910 March 10-1922 February 2 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; T's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; T's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 18:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 18:9)
      re: University of Virginia Presidency, 1904-1905
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; T's n.d. (Box-folder 18:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 18:11)
      re: Professorship of University of Virginia, 1905
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1900-1910 (Box-folder 18:12)
    - J. R. A. Vaughan to Collins Denny 1910 August 26-1911 August 8 (Box-folder 18:13)
    - Francis P. Venable to Collins Denny 1910 October 17-1911 June 13 (Box-folder 18:14)
    - W. E. Vaughan to Collins Denny 1907 February 7-1909 February 23 (Box-folder 18:15)
    - O. E. Vivion to Collins Denny 1910 September 29-1920 June 14 (Box-folder 18:16)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; U's & V's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 18:17)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 18:18)
    - S. H. Wainwright to Collins Denny 1910 May 28-1911 May 6 (Box-folder 18:19)
    - J. K. Waller to Collins Denny 1910 July 23-1911 May 11 (Box-folder 18:20)
    - M. L. Walten to Collins Denny 1906 April 2-1917 July 4 (Box-folder 18:21)
    - S. E. Wasson to Collins Denny 1903 May 20-1921 March 14 (Box-folder 18:22)
    - Bishop R. G. Waterhouse to Collins Denny 1904 June 2-1921 September 22 (Box-folder 18:23)
    - L. Weaver to Collins Denny 1910 September 14-1910 October 4 (Box-folder 18:24)
    - M. Weaver to Collins Denny 1910 November 22-1912 April 12 (Box-folder 18:25)
    - William Webb to Collins Denny 1907 April 1-1917 November 2 (Box-folder 18:26)
    - The Wesley Brotherhood to Collins Denny 1907 August 10-1908 February 14 (Box-folder 18:27)
    - Paul Whitehead to Collins Denny 1903 January 6-1907 March 25 (Box-folder 18:28)
    - Emil C. Wilm to Collins Denny 1903 May 14-1905 July 6 (Box-folder 18:29)
    - R. P. Wilson to Collins Denny 1902 December 12-1903 December 19 (Box-folder 19:1)
    - R. P. Wilson to Collins Denny 1904 January 22-1905 October 20 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - W. M. Wilson to Collins Denny 1910 September 12-1912 May 7 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - John Sharp William to Collins Denny 1904 June 10-1931 June 14 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - President Woodrow Wilson to Collins Denny 1906 April 19-1918 May 30 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - G. B. Winton to Collins Denny 1903 May 7-1911 May 11 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - E. K. Wolfe to Collins Denny 1910 September 26-1910 November 4 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - C. C. Woods to Collins Denny 1910 July 5-1916 November 16 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - W. H. Woof to Collins Denny 1910 July 8-1912 February 26 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - J. W. Worsnop to Collins Denny 1910 May 19-1919 May 13 (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; W's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence: W's 1900-1910 (Box-folder 19:12)
    - Collins Denny to R. P. Wilson n.d. (Box-folder 19:13)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence n.d. (Box-folder 19:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; X, Y, & Z 1900-1910 (Box-folder 19:15)
  - 1911-1922
    - J. B. Adams to Collins Denny 1918 May 31-1921 January 17 (Box-folder 20:1)
    - T. W. Adams to Collins Denny 1914 June 19-1914 December 4 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Henry H. Ahrens to Collins Denny 1918 May 27-1922 August 9 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - R. H. Alderman to Collins Denny 1914 February 17-1918 April 8 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - B. P. Allen to Collins Denny 1913 May 14-1916 March 17 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - B. P. Allen to Collins Denny 1913 May 14-1916 May 17 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; A-Al 1911-1922 (Box-folder 20:6)
    - W. E. Arnold to Collins Denny 1914 February 10-1921 December 5 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Am-Ar 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 20:8)
    - N. G. Augustus to Collins Denny 1920 March 16-1938 January 11 (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; As-Az 1911-1922 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; A 1911-1922 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - S. H. Babcock to Collins Denny 1910 January 8-1912 April 10 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - R. A. Baird to Collins Denny 1911 February 15-1911 July 15 (Box-folder 20:13)
    - W. W. Ball to Collins Denny 1919 February 24-1921 May 7 (Box-folder 20:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ba-Bal 1911-1922 (Box-folder 20:15)
    - G. W. Banks to Collins Denny 1916 February 14-1921 November 12 (Box-folder 20:16)
    - A. H. Bames to Collins Denny 1913 January 25-1920 December 9 (Box-folder 20:17)
    - R. Ira Barnett to Collins Denny 1916 May 27-1918 May 28 (Box-folder 20:18)
    - H. Webb Bays to Collins Denny 1913 September 30-1917 April 25 (Box-folder 20:19)
    - Mamie Bays to Collins Denny 1922 April 25-1938 May 12 (Box-folder 20:20)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Bam-Baz 1911-1922 (Box-folder 20:21)
    - Geo. L. Beale to Collins Denny 1912 October 28-1918 October 26 (Box-folder 20:22)
    - W. G. Beasley to Collins Denny 1912 January 3-1917 January 25 (Box-folder 20:23)
    - B. M. Beckham to Collins Denny 1912 August 9-1917 November 3 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - Dow B. Beene to Collins Denny 1912 October 9-1914 July 19 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Belle Bennett to Collins Denny 1916 June 7-1921 June 21 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - R. H. Bennett to Collins Denny 1913 October 23-1922 May 29 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Albert D. Betts to Collins Denny 1913 December 10-1922 July 27 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - W. A. Betts to Collins Denny 1914 August 1-1920 December 8 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Be's 1911-1922 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - W. R. Bickerstaff to Collins Denny 1916 May 8-1916 September 11 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Albert W. Biggs to Collins Denny 1912 December 30-1914 April 14 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - W. K. Bixby to Collins Denny 1913 April 11-1916 January 22 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - J. T. Blackwood to Collins Denny 1912 November 18-1914 April 24 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Cole L. Blease to Collins Denny 1914 November 7-1929 October 24 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - H. B. Blue to Collins Denny 1912 November 13-1914 April 28 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Bi-Bl 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 21:14)
    - C. L. Bohon to Collins Denny 1919 August 20-1921 May 5 (Box-folder 21:15)
    - George E. Booker to Collins Denny 1912 December 23-1921 February 21 (Box-folder 21:16)
    - J. T. Bosman to Collins Denny 1915 March 17-1916 June 13 (Box-folder 21:17)
    - E. S. Buswell to Collins Denny 1919 December 10-1922 January 5 (Box-folder 21:18)
    - H. K. Boyer to Collins Denny 1913 February 17-1921 July 11 (Box-folder 21:19)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Bo 1911-1922 (Box-folder 21:20)
    - W. D. Bradfield to Collins Denny 1916 August 4-1917 May 7 (Box-folder 21:21)
    - J. M. Bradley to Collins Denny 1911 February 2-1911 August 11 (Box-folder 21:22)
    - John P. Branch to Collins Denny 1914 June 28-1914 July 28 (Box-folder 21:23)
    - L. C. Branscomb to Collins Denny 1914 June 30-1920 March 17 (Box-folder 21:24)
    - F. R. Bridges to Collins Denny 1916 May 3-1920 May 14 (Box-folder 21:25)
    - C. H. Bridges to Collins Denny 1912 September 3-1920 April 3 (Box-folder 21:26)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Bra-Bri 1911-1912 (Box-folder 21:27)
    - W. E. Brock to Collins Denny 1913 October 24-1938 December 20 (Box-folder 21:28)
    - Henry W. Bromley to Collins Denny 1920 April 26-1922 June 2 (Box-folder 21:29)
    - H. B. Brown to Collins Denny 1914 October 7-1919 March 17 (Box-folder 21:30)
    - J. R. Brown to Collins Denny 1913 August 20-1921 May 20 (Box-folder 21:31)
    - R. T. Brown to Collins Denny 1920 April 12-1921 May 27 (Box-folder 21:32)
    - E. N. Broyles to Collins Denny 1920 March 25-1938 April 15 (Box-folder 21:33)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Bro-Bry 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 21:34)
    - James H. Bunch to Collins Denny 1916 January 13-1918 June 19 (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Robert L. Burch to Collins Denny 1917 March 26-1917 November 5 (Box-folder 22:2)
    - S. H. C. Burgin to Collins Denny 1920 September 8-1922 April 4 (Box-folder 22:3)
    - James A. Burrow to Collins Denny 1913 May 12-1921 July 14 (Box-folder 22:4)
    - M. L. Butler to Collins Denny 1914 March 19-1918 March 29 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Bu-By 1911-1922 (Box-folder 22:6)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 22:7)
    - G. E. Cameron to Collins Denny 1919 August 21-1922 January 17 (Box-folder 22:8)